textmessagelol.com 2013-04-03

# 

Effective Date: April 15th, 2012

GENERAL PRIVACY POLICY: 

At textmessagelol.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit textmessagelol.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on textmessagelol.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

TEXTMESSAGELOL.COM's FACEBOOK APPLICATION PRIVACY POLICY

We at textmessagelol.com(“we”) respect your privacy and value the relationship we have with you. Your use of this application is subject to this Privacy Policy. Your use of Facebook in general and your relationship with Facebook are subject to Facebook’s own Privacy Policy and Facebook’s other terms and policies, which Breakinin.com does not control. This Privacy Policy describes how Breakinin.com may use the information we collect with this application on Facebook and with whom we may share it. 

Information We Collect

We may collect two types of personal information with this application: (i) information and content we receive from Facebook that was provided by you or other users to Facebook or was associated by Facebook with a particular user (“Information We Receive From Facebook”) and (ii) information and content you provide directly to us, such as by submitting it to us through a form in this application (“Independent Information”). 

Information We Receive From Facebook 

When you visit the application, it may collect any information you have made visible to “Everyone” on Facebook as well as the information Facebook designates as your publicly available information. This includes your name, profile picture, gender, current city, networks, friend list, and pages you are a fan of. Even if you have not allowed this application access, it may collect Information We Receive From Facebook about you when friends on Facebook allow access to and use the application, subject to your Facebook settings. We use this information to operate the application, such as posting to your wall or sharing with other users. We may share this information on your wall or with other users without your explicit approval. 

Independent Information 

The application may ask you to explicitly provide certain information to us, such as your email address from a pre-defined list to send to your friends. We generally use Independent Information for the same purposes as we use Information We Receive From Facebook. 

How We Share Information We Receive From Facebook 

We may disclose Information We Receive From Facebook to our affiliates and service providers to the extent permitted by Facebook. We will not provide such information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent, but we do not control Facebook’s own use of content and information it collects in relation to your use of this application. We also may share Information We Receive From Facebook with other third parties with your consent. For example, we may share some Information We Receive From Facebook with other users of Facebook, including other users of the application, as described above. 

We may disclose any Information We Receive From Facebook we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. In addition, we may disclose Information We Receive From Facebook when we believe, in our sole discretion, disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with suspected or actual illegal activity. 

Updates To This Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a notice on http://www.flirte.rs/privacy.php to notify you of any significant changes to the Privacy Policy and indicate there and at the top of the Policy when it was most recently updated. 

How to Contact Us 

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy notice, please contact us by email at textmessagelol@boommediallc.com
